Nathani Luvinga

Individual with the ability to follow established procedures and work under little or no supervision; offering technical expertise in programming, Ict systems and application development capabilities. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive



cosmasnathan9@gmail.com

0769191457

P.O.Box 86, Dar es salaam, Tanzania

github.com/drneyx

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science University of Dar es salaam

11/2017 - 08/2020

Dar es salaam-Tanzania

PCM

Kigonsera High school

07/2015 - 05/2017

Ruvuma-Tanzania

Science Subjects

Lyamkena Secondary school

01/2011 - 11/2014 Njombe-Tanzania

All subjects

Mashujaa Primary school

01/2004 - 10/2010 Njombe-Tanzania

WORK EXPERIENCE

Practical Training-software developer

Mbeya head post company

07/2018 - 09/2018

Mbeya-Tanzania

Tasks

- Design process and procedures
- Software development
- Mobile app development

Software developer

My shulesmart Company limited

09/2020 - 11/2020

Dar es salaam

- Analysing software requirements and design
- Software methodologies
- Software development
- Amazon cloud services

REFEREE NO 1

Dr. Baraka Maiseli

barakaezra@udsm.ac.tz

REFEREE NO 2

Dr.Fatma Simba fatmasimba@gmail.com

SKILLS

Interface design and implementation

Database design and administration

Software programming

Project management

Strong interpersonal skills

Communication skills

Excellent analytical skills

PROJECTS

Water distribution management system (03/2020 - 05/2020)

Recommender engine for restaurants in Toronto (06/2020 - 07/2020)

Afic CRM (09/2020 - 10/2020)

Hotel Management system (09/2020 - 10/2020)

SHUTA (android app) (03/2019 - 05/2019)

SmeMarket Web system

Jw company website

Jamii chat app

TECHNICAL LANGUAGE/FRAMEWORKS

Django 90% HTML 97% CSS 80% Javascript 60%

Java 90% Php 60% React native 50% SQL 85%

CERTIFICATES

IBM data science professional certificate

Oracle Autonomous Database Cloud 2019 Certified Specialist

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Foundations 2020 Certified Associate

LANGUAGES

Professional Working Proficiency

Swahili

Native or Bilingual Proficiency